[{"answer": " Why, my friend", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "How's Miss my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Yes", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I don't know no my friend. This is a restaurant. Many people come here", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Yes  yes, if she made that much impression on you, I'm sure it was my friend", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "But she was here", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "In a way that makes everything my business", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes. I was going to tell you to look into your own heart", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "And what is it about, Miss my friend", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "May I ask who gave you his name", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Sister, you can't just go breaking into places. There's a night watchman down there and locks on the door", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " I don't know if I want to go with you or not", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "But I'm not joking", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "But I'm better than a detective. I have an understanding of people", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What was she to you", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I think I understand without your telling me. I know something of your history, my friend. I know that you haven't written for ten years", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "But I like teaching school", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Is Mrs. my friend nice to work for", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Because you are intelligent", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I always thought it was a more intimate relationship", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " I had begun to write again", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You went to see Mrs. Redi... She told you something", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "If it is true  there's all the more reason for you to find my friend", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He loves you, my friend, and you'll have to tell him", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Do you think he knows about this", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He's clever and he's cautious in his way. If he knew I think he'd advise her to do what I want", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " You don't expect me to do that do you", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Tell me what", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Goo", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I won't get lonely", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "She is very young", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It might have", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " I shouldn't wonder, Babe. I shouldn't wonder", "docId": "SeventhVictim.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'll help you to a beer and a sandwich. Come along, babe, come along", "qsentId": 34}]